[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The normal body temperature is 37.5 \u00baC.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name Ursula Andress character\u2019s name in James Bonds Doctor No.", "correct_answer": "Honey Ryder", "incorrect_answers": ["Tiffany Case", "Dominique (Domino) Derval", "Pussy Galore"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1993 movie contains this quote: The young carpenter from Nazareth? I know him well. Promising young man. He died badly.?", "correct_answer": "Needful Things", "incorrect_answers": ["Warlock", "The Prophecy", "In the Mouth of Madness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the largest country in the world?", "correct_answer": "Russia", "incorrect_answers": ["USA", "China", "Canada"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Male Western Grey Kangaroos were nicknamed Stinkers because they have this kind of odor.", "correct_answer": "Curry", "incorrect_answers": ["Sour cabbage", "Garlic", "Gasoline"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mudpuppies breathe through gills when they are young and when they mature they use their lungs.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What makes the Japanese dish called Fugu unique?", "correct_answer": "It is made from poisonous fish.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is prepared from an endangered animal.", "It is prepared from tiger testicles.", "It is made from the beating heart of a snake."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Moons diameter is approximately this long.", "correct_answer": "2,154 miles (3,476 km)", "incorrect_answers": ["2,796 miles (4,500 km)", "5,567 miles (8,960 km)", "7,145 miles (11,500 km)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What plant is used in the preparation of the traditional Arab dish called Toum?", "correct_answer": "Garlic", "incorrect_answers": ["Turnip", "Mustard", "Onion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1993 romantic movie Sleepless in Seattle, Little Jonah compares the laughter of Victoria to the sounds produced by this animal.", "correct_answer": "Hyena", "incorrect_answers": ["Mare", "Sow", "Crow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can overnutrition cause malnutrition?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A group of Earth children help a stranded alien botanist return home is the plot outline of this movie.", "correct_answer": "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial", "incorrect_answers": ["Star Wars: Episode VI - Return of the Jedi", "The Hitch Hikers Guide to the Galaxy", "Cyborg"]}]